{
    "questions": [
        {
            "index": "0",
            "questionText" : "The atomic number for lithium is 17",
            "questionAnswer" : "true"
        },

        {
            "index": "1",
            "questionText" : "The black box in a plane is black",
            "questionAnswer" : "false"
        },

        {
            "index": "2",
            "questionText" : "Prince Harry is taller than Prince William",
            "questionAnswer" : "false"
        },

        {
            "index": "3",
            "questionText" : "The star sign Aquarius is represented by a tiger",
            "questionAnswer" : "true"
        },

        {
            "index": "4",
            "questionText" : "Marrakesh is the capital of Morocco",
            "questionAnswer" : "false"
        },

        {
            "index": "5",
            "questionText" : "Waterloo has the greatest number of tube platforms in London",
            "questionAnswer" : "true"
        },

        {
            "index": "6",
            "questionText" : "There are two parts of the body that can`t heal themselves",
            "questionAnswer" : "false"
        },

        {
            "index": "7",
            "questionText" : "The Great Wall of China is longer than the distance between London and Beijing",
            "questionAnswer" : "true"
        },

        {
            "index": "8",
            "questionText" : "There are five different blood groups",
            "questionAnswer" : "false"
        },

        {
            "index": "9",
            "questionText" : "Australia is wider than the moon",
            "questionAnswer" : "true"
        }
    ]
}